Speaker 0: Alright. Today, I'm gonna go ahead and teach you how you can use digital ocean to host your files. Is there any way you can set up your own RSS feed to support your music or your podcast. So cool thing about Digital Ocean is if you lose the link that I provided, then you'll get, two months worth of hosting for free, two hundred dollars. You're not gonna use that two hundred dollars. You're gonna sign up for the digital ocean spaces, and that's gonna cost you five dollars a month. But if you use that link, then once you've spent twenty five dollars, then I'll get twenty five dollar credit to my account, and that helps pay for any of the hosting stuff I have for the various projects, Ellen Beats, music side project, Keriocaster, split kit, all of that using some of the stuff that Digital Ocean provides. So I really appreciate guys using that link and providing some value back to me. So I'm assuming that you've already used that link. You've signed up. You've created an account we're gonna come into Digital Ocean. We're gonna log in. And I use my GitHub account to log in maybe use your Google account, GitHub, your email, whatever you use, go ahead and get yourself logged in. And the first thing we wanna do is come over here and create a new project. So because we're doing some file hosting, I'm just gonna name my project as file hoster. Then for a description, I don't really need one, but I do need a purpose. That's a requirement, and I'm going to do other, and I'm gonna just label it. As file hosting. So now I'm gonna create the project, and I don't need to remove any of the resources, so I'm gonna skip this. So I've got my project file hoster, and I'm gonna go ahead and start using spaces. So with spaces, it's gonna pick the data center that's closest to you. So I wouldn't, worry about changing that. You can by coming in here but I'm just gonna go ahead and keep it as the one that's closest to me. And for the first one, we're gonna go ahead enable CD in that should help on bandwidth because they'll cache the files. So any files that you don't plan on changing very often, go ahead and put them into this first bucket that we're gonna create and enable the CDN. So that's gonna be MP threes and your images and your chapters. Anything that you think will you won't change within the cash period. We're gonna set your cash period to a week. So any file that you have that you don't plan on changing, go ahead and drop it in here. So let's enable this CDN. And let's go ahead and for our unique name. And you really can create anything that you want. So I'm gonna label this one as static files, music or MSP from music side project. And I'm gonna select the project, and this one's going into file hoster. So I'm gonna go ahead and create that space. Then the next thing I wanna do is because these are files that we want other podcast players to be able to access, wanna come over here to the course configuration, and course is just a safety thing that browsers have that make it so that people can't, you people can't send malicious stuff to your site unless you've got this allowed. So and Other sites can't.
Speaker 0: So cool thing about Digital Ocean is if you lose the link that I provided,
Speaker 0: then you'll get, two months worth of hosting for free, two hundred dollars. You're not gonna use that two hundred dollars.
Speaker 0: You're gonna sign up for the digital ocean spaces, and that's gonna cost you five dollars a month. But if you use that link, then once you've spent twenty five dollars, then I'll get twenty five dollar credit to my account, and that helps pay for any of the hosting stuff I have for the various projects, Ellen Beats, music side project, Keriocaster,
Speaker 0: split kit, all of that using some of the stuff that Digital Ocean provides. So I really appreciate guys using that link and providing some value back to me.
Speaker 0: So I'm assuming that you've already used that link. You've signed up. You've created an account we're gonna come into Digital Ocean. We're gonna log in.
Speaker 0: And I use my GitHub account to log in maybe use your Google account, GitHub, your email, whatever you use, go ahead and get yourself logged in. And the first thing we wanna do is come over here and create a new project.
Speaker 0: So because we're doing some file hosting, I'm just gonna name my project as file hoster.
Speaker 0: Then for a description,
Speaker 0: I don't really need one, but I do need a purpose. That's a requirement, and I'm going to do other, and I'm gonna just label it. As file hosting.
Speaker 0: So now I'm gonna create the project,
Speaker 0: and I don't need to remove any of the resources, so I'm gonna skip this.
Speaker 0: So I've got my project file hoster, and I'm gonna go ahead and start using spaces.
Speaker 0: So with spaces, it's gonna pick the data center that's closest to you. So I wouldn't,
Speaker 0: worry about changing that. You can by coming in here but I'm just gonna go ahead and keep it as the one that's closest to me.
Speaker 0: And for the first one, we're gonna go ahead enable CD in that should help on bandwidth because they'll cache the files. So any files that you don't plan on changing very often,
Speaker 0: go ahead and put them into
Speaker 0: this first bucket that we're gonna create and enable the CDN. So that's gonna be MP threes and your images and your chapters.
Speaker 0: Anything that you think will you won't change within the cash period.
Speaker 0: We're gonna set your cash period to a week. So any file that you have that you don't plan on changing, go ahead and drop it in here. So let's enable this CDN.
Speaker 0: And let's go ahead and for our unique name.
Speaker 0: And you really can create anything that you want. So I'm gonna label this one as
Speaker 0: static
Speaker 0: files,
Speaker 0: music or MSP from music side project.
Speaker 0: And I'm gonna select the project,
Speaker 0: and this one's going into file hoster.
Speaker 0: So I'm gonna go ahead and create that space.
Speaker 0: Then the next thing I wanna do is because these are files that we want other podcast players to be able to access,
Speaker 0: wanna come over here to the course configuration,
Speaker 0: and course is just a safety thing that browsers have that make it so that people can't,
Speaker 0: you people can't send malicious stuff to your site unless
Speaker 0: you've got this allowed.
Speaker 0: So and
Speaker 0: Other sites can't.